How is this happening? Do you guys train
him to do all this? Like, how is this
happening? All right. Oh, no. Don't bite
my beard. That's my toe. That's my toe.
That's my [laughter]
Oh, we got double. What's up, everybody?
I'm Scott Malok. I'm going to be playing
with puppies and answering questions.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Oh my goodness. They're over [music]
being swarmed. Hi. Uh, hidden talents.
I'm a pretty decent golfer and a pretty
decent bowler that most people don't
expect. [music]
I can golf and bowl pretty good.
>> Come back.
>> Not bad. Pretty good.
>> Do I have a favorite puppy? Yeah, this
guy. [music] He's girl guy. He She's He
or she's the best. She's Yeah. Everyone
else is crazy. She's over it. He or
she's over it. I know.
>> What do you think about [music]
>> um I don't know. I'm like super neat
[music] and organized like my locker and
just like I always have things like nice
and neat. Kind of OCD. Not like
clinically, but like I'm very organized.
I [music] like things certain ways.
What? Hey, don't just be crawling. Hey.
always had a passion [music] for like
law enforcement andor military growing
up. Guys, you're disturbing my one
peaceful dog. He just doesn't want to be
bothered.
You're disturbing my guy. [music]
Yeah, just just look at that. He's right
there.
Ooh. [music]
Well, PAT is what, 33 yards? I think I
could do the NFL PAT. Yeah. I like mess
around [music] at practice sometimes and
kick the ball. Yeah. And it's pretty
good. just an athlete
[music]
jumbo package. Wow. Well, [music] no, I
couldn't. They're all the same size, but
basically No, you're sleeping. I won't
bother you. [music] Yeah, we're just
going to We're on the goal line, right?
So, we're all tight.
We're all tight together. Crowd in the
line of scrimmage. I need me. I need a
fullback. Who's the whitest dog in here?
Okay, we're Okay, we're fall start.
False start. Fall start. This puppy.
[music]
Oh, that was amazing. They were so kind,
welcoming, you know, to have me on set.
>> What about special teams coverage?
>> Special [music] what?
>> Kathy was amazing to work with. The rest
of the cast was amazing to work with. It
[music] was really fun. It was It was
something that I heard that she wasn't
really excited to [music] do, but like
as we got going, I like warmed her up a
bit a little bit and we started having
fun. kind of like these guys, huh? And
uh it was just amazing. [music] I'm
trying to get back there and we can do
it again for sure.
Furball.
Pineapple on pizza. I'm not about it.
Nope. It's not allowed. Not allowed.
I'd say [music] I'd say quarterbacks are
probably the most kept to themselves. O
line is probably the most tight-knit. O
line and [music] Dline are always pretty
close. And you know, we always spend
time together, but [music] I think those
are obviously the position rooms that
have a lot of, you know, high volume of
players. Whoa. Hey, we're not doing
that. Skilled players are probably
always deemed as the coolest or got the
most swag or this that or another. And
probably tight ends are at the bottom of
that list. Running backs [music] are
also in that category skill group. So, I
don't know. Yeah,
probably brushes. Oh my goodness. All
right.
Oh, hi.
Funniest.
I mean, Dion's kind of funny, but that's
just [music] cuz he acts a fool. What do
you say? Who's the funniest? I think
this guy's the funniest.
Favorite line from any movie. H I'll
give a line from [music] my favorite
movie. Do it. And then another one I was
thinking of is aim for the bushes. If
you know, you know.
Biggest misconception about football
players probably that [music] we're
dumb. Hey, what are we doing? I'm being
attacked. Yeah, that's We're pretty
intelligent. There's a lot to have to
know. Oh,
whoa. Get him. Get him.
Three things that I couldn't live live
without.
Who what couldn't [music] I live
without? My family. Couldn't live
without my family and couldn't live
without food and water and um what could
you guys not live without,
huh? Don't need a phone. Money. Money is
nice ice having got to be able to do
[music] things provide. I don't know. I
haven't gave that much thought yet. That
much thought. I'm distracted. [music]
I'm distracted.
I don't I wouldn't say anything
surprised me. I have a nephew and I
[music] spent a lot of time with him
when he was a baby, but I just
Oh, no.
>> Clean up on three. I wouldn't say there
anything that surprised me. I just
[music] would say it's just like it's
like even when he cries, I'm just happy.
Like I don't even care. He's cry. Like
it's just like it's still [music]
he's he's cute when he's crying. He's
cute when he's crying. It's just pure
bliss. Just pure pure bliss. Pure bliss.
Share the toys. [music] Share the toys.
Not my nose.
JJ Watt in high school. [music] I
played, you know, DN and, you know,
defensive line and I like would watch
his highlights [music] and everything.
And I actually was able to he he came
here to the bowl and did an interview
with uh Joey and Khalil and Coach
Harbaugh and Coach [music] Herbert
and I was there. Didn't belong there. I
definitely wasn't allowed. Shouldn't
have been there, but I was able to meet
him and and shake his hand. Oh my
goodness.
>> Oh my Cherry. Oh, I just took off your
Come here.
Most memorable fan interaction. Somebody
drew a sketch of me [music] like at
training camp. Like it was one of those
fans and they had a sketch of like a
[music] portrait and that was kind of
cool. Got a little like portrait. I
thought that was kind of cool and nice
of them to do. Hey, can you chew on this
instead of my toes? Thanks.
When TJ Jeff said, "Uh, y'all going to
Vegas after the game?" And we were in
Vegas. That was really weird. I don't
>> Hey, y'all boys going to Vegas after the
game?
>> I didn't laugh, but that was like
[music] got some other people to laugh,
but I thought that was kind of weird.
Yeah, mentally, I mean, you know, you
have all three playbooks, offense,
defense, special teams.
you know, you [music] don't really get
to sit down like as soon as you know,
let's say we punt, like I'm just walking
down to the defensive, you know, they're
right there on the sideline ready to
take the field and just got to go walk
over there and I don't really get time
to hear the adjustments [music] or
coaching points really of anything. I
try my best like during a TV timeout,
but you know, just trying to master it
all, you know, you know, mastering three
positions is it's a lot harder than just
one.
My [music] guy here. What's this guy or
girl's name? Is Almond. Almond.
Yeah. This is the sweetest. He's like,
he or she's like, I'm I don't want I'm
[music] Take me away. Hey, don't chew.
No.
Why can't you be like your brother or
sister here? You, Almond, are the best.
You're the best. I'm sorry that I have
to leave you, but
>> [sighs]
>> I'm sorry. I have to leave you. He's
like, "Oh, I Where'd you go?" I know.
He's I know. I'm sorry. He's like,
"Okay, I'll go over here now." Perfect.
And perfect. My work here is done. Look
at You're welcome. I'll send you an
invoice. Yeah. For my work here. [music]
>> [music]